heritagesports.eu 2017-12-25

# Privacy Policy - Heritage Sports

**General Provisions**

This privacy policy sets out how The Website uses and protects any information that is submitted to us. We are committed to ensuring the privacy of the information collected through our site. The Website does not intend to collect information, unless you as a visitor choose to provide us the information for communication and/or providing you with ongoing updates.

**Information Collection**

Visitors of our site do not have to submit any personally identifiable information to use/view our site. The Website does not collect personally identifiable information unless visitors specifically and voluntarily provide it. Personally identifiable information may consist of, but not limited to, Name, Job Title, Company Name, Company Address, Email Address, Telephone/Mobile and Fax Numbers.

**Cookies**

To ensure that our site is well managed and to facilitate improved experience, cookies (text files stored in user’s browser) are used for collecting data and tracking visitors through information like IP address, domain, browser type and pages visited. Such information is used to analyze number of visitors and enable us to serve in an effective and efficient way. The cookies are not used for collecting personal information such as name, email etc. Visitors can reject cookies through browser configuration, however some part of the website may be inaccessible if cookies are blocked.

**Information Use**

Personal information submitted via our site is used only for communication, as intended by the visitor when submitting the information. The Website uses the information for improving your user experience.

**Third Party Disclosure**

The Website does not share personal information with third parties unless it is required for processing related to third party services that the Website uses for its business purpose. The Website obeys and respects international privacy laws and ensures that personal information is handled with due care as required by such regulations.

**Change to this policy**

The Website reserves the right to modify this privacy policy at any time. To ensure this policy remains effective and feasible, the Website shall periodically review and make changes without prior notice to its visitors. Visitors are required on their own to check for any updates made to this policy before providing personal information

**Queries**

If you have queries regarding the privacy while using our site, please direct them to us via phone or email.
